well IC lomard is a stock to focus on
now clsa has come out with a report on
this stock and it's a positive one as
well now they have actually upgraded the
rating on IC Lombard from outperform to
buy and kept the Target price at
1,470 per share now they see multiple uh
triggers in place that could actually
reverse the underperformance of around
31 to 36% that has been seen in the
stock over the past 18 months market
share losses uh the trend could see a
reversal in fact the company has gained
market share breaking its long streak of
market share losses in fact they've also
outpaced private payers in terms of
health premiums and they're expecting to
see a 15% tagger in the premiums from fi
23 to 25 apart from that valuations were
previously stretched especially over fi9
to fi21 when the company delivered slow
premium growth but valuations are
appearing to be most reasonable now
given the under performance of 31 to 36%
as I just mentioned so healthy premium
growth recovery reversal of market share
losses expected scale up of uh the
retail Health both as well as the
expectance of the under performance to
reverse a positive note coming in from
CLC they've given a thumbs up to IC
lombar they've upgraded their rating
from outperform to buy but the stock is
definitely reing under pressure today
with the market